Introduction:

Experienced in building teams in highly competitive and combative environments with the ability to bridge gaps with interpersonal skills. Very good at meeting new people, negotiating, communicating, listening, and presenting publically.

I am enthusiastic and self-motivated with a strong sense of consistency in everything I do. I enjoy logic, researching, KYC, leadership, multi-cultural & cross functional teams, coding, sales, entertaining & connecting people together.

Studying at 50% capacity, working as consultant broker, member of the housing board and having an ecommerce store all involve working with people, in person and remotely. I'm organised, efficient and level headed.

Work Experience:

04/2024 - Present

BRF Taffeln1 - Housing Association Board Member

As a housing association board member of a 100 apartment large complex. I have taken responsibility to oversee the management and strategic direction of the community. This involves working towards various governance requirements, financial management of the association, community engagement and maintenance and development of the premises.

I take a large responsibility over the community engagement, meeting with apartment owners and coordinating efforts to revitalise the 60+ year old premises.

04/2022 - Present

TEKsystems - Talent Specialist & BDR

Working towards the financial institutions around Sweden, I am responsible for building networks of professionals in various areas of IT and connecting them with relevant assignments. This involves continually sourcing, meeting and presenting to contractors, consultant agencies, hiring managers and freelancers. Participate in supplier contract negotiations with legal teams for favourable and clear outcomes.

Additionally, I am responsible for meeting managers with active requirements to get better insights into their needs and overall initiatives utilising COPE framework, presenting potential candidates and providing market insights into their specific needs. Lastly, I am responsible for continuous dialogue with teams of consultants to gain continued engagement and commitment as well as solve countless issues & gain additional business insights.

11/2021 - Present

Epiphany Development AB - Own Company

Together with my partner, we own and operate an e-commerce store catered to specific products with targeted marketing channels. Identifying key products, negotiation with social media profiles, suppliers, and clients with strategic planning of product marketing efforts as key responsibilities.

06/2019 - 01/2020 **AME Trade Ltd. - Consulting Sales & Project Manager**

Contracted to co-lead in organising and delivering the 2nd Ethiopian International Mining Conference & Exhibition on behalf of the Ministry of Mining and Petroleum.

The event attracted 300+ mining executives, 9 corporate sponsors with over 320,000 GBP in sponsorships and a range of gemstone, heavy machinery and mining companies to the exhibition in a 6 month timeframe.

10/2017 - 03/2018 **Ulendo Travel Group - Consulting Business Developer**

> Short term contract established to aid the company in developing business processes, organising and running events, renegotiate supplier agreements to lower expenses, calculate opportunity costs of investments & manage fleet of 10 vehicles and drivers.

04/2017 - 10/2017 Mabuya Camp - Consulting Business Developer

> Short term contract established to aid the questhouse in developing business processes, lower expenses through strategic renegotiation with suppliers, investigating accounting documents to identify discrepancies and potential theft, increasing earnings with event organising and collecting on bad debt.

10/2012 - 02/2017 **OropaFX & AquaSound - Account Manager & Retention Sales**

As a Forex Trading Account Manager, I was responsible for the general support and guidance for key clients. Additionally, I was responsible for account recovery in instances where clients investments turned negative. This involved building relationships with disgruntled clients, creating trading strategies and getting clients to reinvest.

Education:

04/2024 - Present **Code Institute - FullStack Development Diploma** This is a self-motivated course in frontend and backend development to give me better insights into the development tools and how they interact with IT infrastructure.

01/2021 - 01/2022 **Southampton University - BA International Business**

Management

Dissertation with a focus on "Fostering Change Readiness"

07/2018 - 06/2020 YRGO College - Business Management Diploma

07/2001 - 06/2008 Alice Smith School, Malaysia

References:

Available Upon Request

Curriculum Vitae: Bjorn Connor Bishop - Business Development Representative